<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on WORKSHOP ON EXCITED-STATE METHODS (Toulouse, 4-6 Apr 2023)</title>
    <link>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on WORKSHOP ON EXCITED-STATE METHODS (Toulouse, 4-6 Apr 2023)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>loos@irsamc.ups-tlse.fr (PTEROSOR)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>loos@irsamc.ups-tlse.fr (PTEROSOR)</webMaster><atom:link href="https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/map/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>loos@irsamc.ups-tlse.fr (PTEROSOR)</author>
      <guid>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/map/</guid>
      <description>The conference will be held in the Auditorium of Le Village near the city center of Toulouse. The address is 31 Allée Jules Guesde 31000 TOULOUSE. Toulouse is an amazing city with many monuments to visit and food to taste (like cassoulet!). For more info, visit Tourism in Toulouse. Here is a selection of monuments you do not want to miss. Note that there are all within walking distance from the workshop venue:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Participants</title>
      <link>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/participants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>loos@irsamc.ups-tlse.fr (PTEROSOR)</author>
      <guid>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/participants/</guid>
      <description>List of participants Giuseppe Barca (Australian National University, Australia) Stefano Battaglia (U of Zurich, Switzerland) Timothy Berkelbach (Columbia U, US) Xavier Blase (Institut Neel, France) Katharina Boguslawski (Nicolaus Copernicus U, Poland) George Booth (King&amp;rsquo;s College, UK) Hugh Burton (Oxford, UK) TBC Andreea Filip (Cambridge, UK) Claudia Filippi (U of Twente, Netherland) Emmanuel Fromager (U of Strasbourg, France) Peter Gill (U of Sydney, Australia) Tim Gould (Griffith U, Australia) Emmanuel Giner (Sorbonne U, France) So Hirata (U of Illinois, US) Joshua Hollett (U of Winnipeg, Canada) Denis Jacquemin (U of Nantes, France) Thomas Jagau (KU Leuven, Belgium) Joohno Lee (Columbia U, US) Eduard Matito (Donostia, Spain) Nick Mayhall (Virginia Tech, US) Carlos Mejuto Zaera (SISSA, Italy) Eric Neuscamman (Berkeley, US) Kasia Pernal (Lodz U, Poland)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posters</title>
      <link>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/posters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>loos@irsamc.ups-tlse.fr (PTEROSOR)</author>
      <guid>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/posters/</guid>
      <description>Abdallah Ammar (U of Toulouse, France) Transcorrelated Configuration Interaction applied to excited states of molecules
Filip Cernatic (U of Strasbourg, France) TBA
Florian Matz (KU Leuven, Belgium) Theoretical Treatment of Molecular Auger Decay with Non-Hermitian Quantum Chemistry
David Amblard (Institut Neel, France) Optimal representation for electronic susceptibility
Gabriele Riva (U of Toulouse, France) TBA
Fabris Kossoski (U of Toulouse, France) TBA
Raul Quintero (U of Toulouse, France) TBA
Sara Giarrusso (U of Toulouse, France) Shape of the Møller-Plesset adiabatic connection integrand for a model diatomic system at different correlation regimes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>loos@irsamc.ups-tlse.fr (PTEROSOR)</author>
      <guid>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/presentations/</guid>
      <description>Invited Speakers Giuseppe Barca (Australian National University, Australia) TBA
Stefano Battaglia (U of Zurich, Switzerland) TBA
Timothy Berkelbach (Columbia U, US) TBA
Xavier Blase (Institut Neel, France) GW and Bethe-Sapeter calculations embedded in very large scale dielectric environment
Katharina Boguslawski (Nicolaus Copernicus U, Poland) TBA
George Booth (King&amp;rsquo;s College, UK) A fresh perspective on Green&amp;rsquo;s function methods
Hugh Burton (Oxford, UK) TBC TBA
Andreea Filip (Cambridge, UK) Quantum Monte Carlo Ideas for Near-Term Quantum Computing Algorithms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>loos@irsamc.ups-tlse.fr (PTEROSOR)</author>
      <guid>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/planning/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, April 4, 2023 TIME EVENT 9:00 - 9:30 Welcome coffee SESSION 1 Chair: Pierre-Francois Loos 9:30 - 10:00 So Hirata - Finite-temperature many-body perturbation theory for electrons and its low-temperature catastrophe 10:00 - 10:30 Giuseppe Barca - Title 10:30 - 11:00 Coffee break 11:00 - 11:30 Nick Mayhall - Excited state calculations with Tensor Product State Selected CI (TPSCI) 11:30 - 12:00 Hugh Burton- Title 12:00 - 12:30 Joohno Lee - Title 12:30 - 14:00 Lunch break &amp;amp; Poster SESSION 2 Chair: Raul Quintero 14:00 - 14:30 Lucia Reining - Title 14:30 - 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>loos@irsamc.ups-tlse.fr (PTEROSOR)</author>
      <guid>https://pfloos.github.io/PTEROSOR_midterm_workshop/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>MAIN SPONSOR This workshop has received funding from the European Research Council (ERC) under the European Union&amp;rsquo;s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme (Grant agreement No. 863481).
OTHER SPONSORS CNRS LCPQ FERMI UPS </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
